7 days, seven Atarangi snacks. It's day
four and today we don't have only just
one product. Have two different drinks.
We have Moya popping boba in luchi and
mango. We are going to try these. These
were very
because boba. We usually drink in boba
cafes and stuff, but I'm quite not
sure. So, let's try it. I love luchi
flavor. So, we are going to try this
first.
Smells like your mou luchi
flavor. Oh yes, I can see the popping
boba. Ai quantity. I got this for 100
rupees like one can for 100 rupees. And
usually bobas are up to 150
200ish. Nice. Usual moui
drink obviously. Now, let's try the
popping boba. These are the popping bob
bars. M. These are actually good. I
usually don't prefer popping bobas
because they're too too tangy and
artificial, but this one is really nice.
A very nice drink. I would rate this a
solid 9 on 10. I really like it. It was
pretty partial because luchy flavor, but
I'm not sure about the mango flavors.
So, let's give this a try.
It tastes like
maza. No, it actually tastes like
fruity. If you know, you know. Fruity
maza. Different taste. This is how the
color looks like. It's pretty artificial
color. But how it
looks my favorite because it is kind of
artificial. Liiiala much better if you
like moi. So, I would rate the mango one
maybe six on good refreshing drink, but
I won't ever bite this flavor. I would
rather go for the luchi flavor because I
really love luchi. That's it